AFSCME, District Council 37 Photographs PHOTOS.247
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VII: Negatives, [1948]-[2003].
  - Subseries E: Locals Negatives, [1967]-[1999].
    - Local 420 (III), Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 420 [41509], Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 420 [3], Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 420 [3A], Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 420 [3B], Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 420: City Hospitals Exposes (PEP) (I), [1967-1968] (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 420: City Hospitals Exposes (PEP) (II), [1967-1968] (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 420: City Hospitals Exposes (PEP) (III), [1967-1968] (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 420: City Hospitals Exposes (PEP) (IV), [1967-1968] (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 420: City Hospitals Exposes (PEP) (V), [1967-1968] (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 420: City Hospitals Exposes (PEP) (VI), [1967-1968] (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 420: City Hospitals Exposes (PEP) (VII), [1967-1968] (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 420: City Hospitals Exposes (PEP) (VIII), [1967-1968] (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 420: City Hospitals Exposes (PEP) (IX), [1967-1968] (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 420: City Hospitals Exposes (PEP) (X), [1967-1968] (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 420: City Hospitals Exposes (PEP) - "Greenpoint", [1967-1968] (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 420: City Hospitals Exposes (PEP) - "Sea View", [1967-1968] (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 420: City Hospitals Exposes (PEP) [8784], [1967-1968] (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 768: "Helen Smith Dinner - 1981" (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 924, Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 924: "Negs 1 District Council", Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 924 [#2], Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 924 [#4]/[#7], Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 924 [#8]/[#9], Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 924 [#10]/[#11], Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 957, Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 957 [52099-1], Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 957 [52099-3], Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 957 [52099-4], Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 957 [52099-5], Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 957 [52099-6], Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 983, Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 983: "George Wetherall for Nick Cifuni", Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 1070, Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 1070 [23236-1], Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 1070 [23236-2,3], Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 1070 [23256-1], Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 1070 [23256-2], Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 1087, Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 1320, Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 1482: "DC 37 7 DOBBS", Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 1485, Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 1501, Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 1507 [1-2], Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 1507 [3], Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 1549, Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 1597 (I), Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 1597 (II), Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 1597 (III), Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 1597 (IV), Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 1597 (V), Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 1597 [8], Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 1597: "Local dinner" [2], Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 1597: "Elev Ops", Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 1597: "Shop Stew. Class" [22A-B], Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 1597: "Shop Stew. Class" [22C-D], Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Local 2021: "Dorothy Reddick Retirement", Undated (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Blue Collar Division- Dotter Series (Locals 375, 1320, 1931) [645551-1,2], [1999] (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Blue Collar Division- Dotter Series (Locals 375, 1320, 1931) [645551-3,4], [1999] (Box 58, Carton 4)
    - Blue Collar Division- Dotter Series (Locals 375, 1320, 1931) [645551-5,6], [1999] (Box 58, Carton 4)
  - Subseries F: Locals 4x5 Negatives, [1963]-[1968].
    - Local 372 (11 negatives), Undated (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Local 372 (2 negatives), [1976?] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Local 420: "Memorial near bridge" (Memorial Service for Victims of Bus Accident- Welfare Island), [Mar 14, 1963] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Local 420 [357685/1-2] (2 negatives), Undated (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Local 420: City Hospitals Exposes (PEP), [1967-1968] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Local 420, Undated (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Local 768, Undated (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Local 1113, Undated (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Local 1320, Undated (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Local 1482, Undated (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Local 1549 (4 negatives), Undated (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Local 1549: Hospitals Chapter Newsletter (3 negatives), Undated (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Local 1549: Polaroid negative (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Local 1783 (12 negatives), Undated (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Local 2507 (3 negatives), Undated (Box 59, Carton 3)
  - Subseries G: DC 37 History Negatives, [1963]-[1972].
    - Events: Spring Leadership Conference, [Apr 1963] (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Events: Constitution Revision Committee Hearings, [1965] (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Events: City Employees Rally--Madison Square Garden (I), [May 23, 1967] (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Events: City Employees Rally--Madison Square Garden (II), [May 23, 1967] (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Events: Local 924 Meetings, [Mar 20, 1968] (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Events: Post-King Assassination Marches--Memphis, 1-2, [Apr 1968] (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Events: Post-King Assassination Marches--Memphis, 4-5, [Apr 1968] (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Events: Post-King Assassination Marches--Memphis, 6-7, [Apr 1968] (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Events: Post-King Assassination Marches--Memphis, 8-9, [Apr 1968] (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Events: Post-King Assassination Marches--Memphis, 10-11, [Apr 1968] (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Events: Post-King Assassination Marches--Memphis, 13 & 15, [Apr 1968] (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Events: Post-King Assassination Marches--Memphis, 16-17, [Apr 1968] (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Events: Post-King Assassination Marches--Memphis, 69-70, [Apr 1968] (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Events: Lillian Roberts Jail Protest, [Dec 1968] (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Events: Labor-Student Coalition for Peace Anti-War Rally, [May 1970] (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Events: Family Day, [Jun 1970] (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Events: [Family Day?], [Jun 1970?] (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Events: Conference of Black Trade Unionists--Chicago, [Sep 1972] (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Events: Local 376 Demonstration, Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Events: [Voter Registration Drive], Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Events: Unidentified, Demonstrations & Rallies, Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Events: Unidentified [Clericals?], Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Events: Unidentified, Conferences/Meetings/Elections, Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Events: Unidentified, Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Events: Unidentified, Conferences/Meetings/Elections (I), Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Events: Unidentified, Conferences/Meetings/Elections (II), Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Events: Unidentified, Conferences/Meetings/Elections (III), Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Events: Unidentified, Conferences/Meetings/Elections (IV), Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Events: Unidentified, Conferences/Meetings/Elections (V), Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Events: Unidentified, Other, Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Officers and Staff: Victor Gotbaum, Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Officers and Staff: Victor Gotbaum at Citywide Negotiations, Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Officers and Staff: Lillian Roberts (I), Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Officers and Staff: Lillian Roberts (II), Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Officers and Staff: Former Staff, Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Officers and Staff: [Former Staff?], Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Members: 50,000th Member, [Sep 1967] (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Members: Department of Parks (I), [1970s] (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Members: Department of Parks (II), Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Members: Department of Parks (III), Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Members: Department of Parks (IV), Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Members: Department of Parks (V), Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Members: Department of Parks (VI), Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Members: Department of Parks (VII), Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - [Members: Department of Parks?], Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Members: [Members on the Job?] (I), Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Members: [Members on the Job?] (II), Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Members: [Members on the Job?] (III), Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - Members: [Members on the Job?] (IV), Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - AFSCME: Executive Board, [Feb 1963] (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - AFSCME: [New York State Legislative Committee] (I), Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - AFSCME: [New York State Legislative Committee] (II), Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - AFSCME: [New York State Legislative Committee] (III), Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - AFSCME: [New York State Legislative Committee] (IV), Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - AFSCME: District Council 50 (I), Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - AFSCME: District Council 50 (II), Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - AFSCME: District Council 50 (III), Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - AFSCME: District Council 50 (IV), Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - AFSCME: District Council 50 (V), Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - AFSCME: District Council 50 "382" (I), Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - AFSCME: District Council 50 "382" (II), Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - AFSCME: District Council 50 "Bronx State 8/68", [Aug 1968] (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - AFSCME: District Council 50 "Buffalo/Seneca/Jan '69" (I), [Jan 1969] (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - AFSCME: District Council 50 "Buffalo/Seneca/Jan '69" (II), [Jan 1969] (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - AFSCME: District Council 50 "Central Islip Laundry 9/68" (I), [Sep 1968] (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - AFSCME: District Council 50 "Central Islip Laundry 9/68" (II), [Sep 1968] (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - AFSCME: District Council 50 "Creedmoor/Oct '68", [Oct 1968] (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - AFSCME: District Council 50 "Creedmoor" [?], Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - AFSCME: District Council 50 "Letchworth", Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - AFSCME: District Council 50 "Pilgrim", Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - AFSCME: District Council 50 "Rockland State/Oct 1968" (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - AFSCME: District Council 50 "Rome/Marcy/Utica Aug 1968" (I) (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - AFSCME: District Council 50 "Rome/Marcy/Utica Aug 1968" (II) (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - AFSCME: District Council 50 "Rome/Marcy/Utica Aug 1968" (III) (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - AFSCME: District Council 50 "Security Unit/Correction Officers", Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - AFSCME: District Council 50 "Tina Wallace Profile" (I), Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - AFSCME: District Council 50 "Tina Wallace Profile" (II), Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - AFSCME: District Council 50 "Troopers", Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - AFSCME: District Council 50 "Wassaic/Harlem Valley/Oct '68" (I), [Oct 1968] (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - AFSCME: District Council 50 "Wassaic/Harlem Valley/Oct '68" (II), [Oct 1968] (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - AFSCME: District Council 50 "Western Tier/Aug '68" (I), [Aug 1968] (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - AFSCME: District Council 50 "Western Tier/Aug '68" (II), [Aug 1968] (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - AFSCME: District Council 50 "Willard", Undated (Box 59, Carton 1)
    - AFSCME: District Council 50 "Willowbrook Demo + Unit Symbols Oct '68", [Oct 1968] (Box 59, Carton 1)
  - Subseries H: DC 37 History 4x5 Negatives, [1948]-[1989].
    - Events: Rally for Raises, [Apr 1954] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Events: Cafeteria Workers Strike (Local 1933), [1955] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Events: Department of Parks Election, [Jan 1956] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Events: Local 924 Demonstation, [May 28, 1957] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Events: Metropolitan Museum of Art Strike, [Jun 1958] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Events: Youth March for Integrated Schools, [Oct 1958] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Events: New York City Board of Estimate Hearings/Salary Appeals, [1958] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Events: "Bermuda Day" Rally (I), [Mar 31, 1959] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Events: "Bermuda Day" Rally (II), [Mar 31, 1959] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Events: Labor Day Parade, [1959] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Events: Motor Vehicle Operators (MVO) Demonstration, [Nov 1962] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Events: March on Washington, [Aug 1963] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Events: March on Washington- Frames 970, 973, 988, 995, 1009, 1011, [Aug 1963] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Events: Fall Conference (113 negatives), [1963] (Box 59, Carton 3)
    - Events: Welfare Strike (Local 371) (3 negatives), [1965] (Box 59, Carton 4)
    - Events: City Employees Rally--Madison Square Garden (3 negatives), [May 23, 1967] (Box 59, Carton 4)
    - Events: Office of Collective Bargaining (OCB) Creation, [1967] (Box 59, Carton 4)
    - Events: Post-King Assassination Marches--Memphis, 71, [Apr 1968] (Box 59, Carton 4)
    - Events: Post-King Assassination Marches--Memphis (3 negatives), [Apr 1968] (Box 59, Carton 4)
    - Events: Lillian Roberts Jail Protest (2 negatives), [Dec 1968] (Box 59, Carton 4)
    - Events: DC 37 25th Anniversary (2 negatives), [1969] (Box 59, Carton 4)
    - Events: Local 420 Strike, [Aug 1976] (Box 59, Carton 4)
    - Events: Lobby Day Campaign, Tier 4 Reform--Albany, [1989] (Box 59, Carton 4)
    - Events: Local 371 SSEU Demonstration, Undated (Box 59, Carton 4)
    - Events: Elections--"Unity Slate Victory", Undated (Box 59, Carton 4)
    - Events: Unidentified, Demonstration, Undated (Box 59, Carton 4)
    - Events: Unidentified (22 negatives), Undated (Box 59, Carton 4)
    - Officers and Staff: Jerry Wurf, Undated (Box 59, Carton 4)
    - Officers and Staff: Calogero Taibi, Undated (Box 59, Carton 4)
    - Officers and Staff: Victor Gotbaum (2 negatives), Undated (Box 59, Carton 4)
    - Officers and Staff: Victor Gotbaum--"Vic- Haber Coll. Bging", Undated (Box 59, Carton 4)
    - Officers and Staff: [Harry Gray?] (5 negatives), Undated (Box 59, Carton 4)
    - Officers and Staff: Former Staff--Ed Maher [Job no. 33094], Undated (Box 59, Carton 4)
    - Members: Police Civilians, [1980] (Box 59, Carton 4)
    - Members: [Members on the Job] (21 negatives), Undated (Box 59, Carton 4)
    - Members: [Members?] (10 negatives), Undated (Box 59, Carton 4)
    - AFSCME: "SCME Program for 1957", [1956?] (Box 59, Carton 4)
    - Other Individuals/Organizations: United Farm Workers, Undated (Box 59, Carton 4)
    - Other Individuals/Organizations: [Robert F. Wagner, Jr.?], Undated (Box 59, Carton 4)
    - Group Portraits: Joint Board of Hospital Locals (AFSCME), [1948] (Box 59, Carton 4)
    - Group Portraits: Unidentified (2 negatives), Undated (Box 59, Carton 4)
  - Subseries I: DC 37 Subject Files Negatives, [1963]-[1975].
    - Education: "Spring Conference April 6, 1963"/"Cornell Grad 9/26/75 issue", [Apr 1963, Sep 1975] (Box 59, Carton 2)
    - Nurses' Aides Upgrading Program, Undated (Box 59, Carton 2)
    - Nurses' Aides Upgrading Program: OB-GYNs (I), Undated (Box 59, Carton 2)
    - Nurses' Aides Upgrading Program: OB-GYNs (II), Undated (Box 59, Carton 2)
    - Nurses' Aides Upgrading Program: OB-GYNs (III), Undated (Box 59, Carton 2)
    - Office of Collective Bargaining, Undated (Box 59, Carton 2)
    - Quality of Work Life Committee (QWL), Undated (Box 59, Carton 2)
    - Quality of Work Life Committee (QWL): "Parks ER Negatives", Undated (Box 59, Carton 2)
  - Subseries J: DC 37 Subject Files 4x5 Negatives, [1957]-[1975].
    - DC 37 Headquarters (Elk Street), [1957] (Box 59, Carton 4)
    - Safety--"Noise Article", [1975] (Box 59, Carton 4)
    - Summer Camp (2 negatives), Undated (Box 59, Carton 4)
  - Subseries K: General Subject Files Negatives, Undated.
    - Cemetery, Undated (Box 59, Carton 2)
  - Subseries L: Oversize Negatives, [1968]-[1989].
    - PEP Vol. 10 No. 12 Issue: Oct 10, 1969 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - PEP Vol. 11 No. 6 Issue: May 8, 1970 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - PEP Vol. 15 No. 10 Issue: Jun 7, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - PEP Vol. 25 No. 1 Issue: Jan 27, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - PEP Vol. 29 No. 7 Issue: Apr 29, 1988 (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - PEP Vol. 30 No. 20 Issue: Nov 24, 1989 (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - Local 154, Undated (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - Local 924, Undated (Box 56, Folder 20)
    - Local 983 (5 negatives), Undated (Box 56, Folder 21)
    - Local 1113 (4 negatives), Undated (Box 56, Folder 22)
    - Local 1549, Undated (Box 56, Folder 23)
    - DC 37 History Events: "Bermuda Day" Rally (Copy Negative), Undated (Box 56, Folder 24)
    - DC 37 History Events: Post-King Assassination Marches--Memphis, [Apr 1968] (Box 56, Folder 25)
    - DC 37 History Officers & Staff: Victor Gotbaum, Undated (Box 56, Folder 26)
    - DC 37 History Members: "Joe De Canio + Laborer Gang" (Copy Negative), Undated (Box 56, Folder 27)
    - DC 37 History Members on the Job, [Apr 11, 1969] (Box 56, Folder 28)
    - DC 37 History AFSMCE: District Council 50, Undated (Box 56, Folder 29)
  - Subseries M: Miscellaneous Negatives, Undated.
    - Unidentified, Undated (Box 59, Carton 2)
- Series VIII: Slides, [1963]-1989.
  - Public Employee Press: Jun 6, 1975; Sep 14, 1984; Dec 4, 1992, [1975-1992] (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Locals: 299, 1549, [1963], undated (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Locals: 1549, [1989], undated (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Events: MVO/Pension Strikes, Fiscal Crisis, Labor Day Parade, New York City Bargaining, [1962]-1987 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Events: NFL Players Strike Support, Woodhull Hospital Demonstration, Lincoln Hospital Anniversary, Housing Conference, 1987, undated (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Members on the Job: 911, Hospitals, Clerical, Police Department, 1978-1980, undated (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Members on the Job: Police Department (cont.), Highways, 1979, undated (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Members on the Job: Highways (cont.), Various, 1978-1979, undated (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - City Agencies and Departments [QWL?]: Department of Environmental Protection (DEP); DEP Picnic; Department of Health Education Fair; Department of Housing, Preservation and Development (HPD); Human Resources Administration (HRA), [1987]-1988, undated (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - WNYC; Women's Committee; Education Fund; Mexico Relief; Jamaica Relief; Safety; DC 37 Banners, [1975]-1989, undated (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - DC 37 Subjects Unknown, 1988, undated (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - New York City; FDNY; Albany; Washington, DC Scenes, 1970-1983, undated (Box 50, Folder 12)